🗷 sgchi@purdue.edu | 🎢 engineering.purdue.edu/people/seunggeun.chi.1 | 🖸 sgchi | 🛅 seunggeun-chi-963050153 | 🎓 Seunggeun Chi

Research Interests

My research interests lie in **Machine Learning** and its applications to real-world problems. **Representation Learning** in **Computer Vision** problems is my primary study. My research also spans over **Combinatorial Optimization** problems which aim to extract rules by applying **Reinforcement Learning**.

Education

Purdue University West Lafayette, U.S.

Ph.D. STUDENT IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Aug. 2021 - current

• C-Design Lab, Advisor: Karthik Ramani

Seoul National University Seoul, S.Korea

M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Mar. 2019 - Aug. 2021

• Optimization Lab, Advisor: ByungRo Moon

Seoul National University Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Mar. 2013 - Feb. 2019

• Computer Architecture Lab, Advisor: SangLyul Min

Publications

Conference Proceedings

- S. Chi*, H. Chi*, Q. Huang, K. Ramani. Skeleton-ODE: Learning Representation by Predicting the Future for Online Skeleton-based Action Recognition *IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2023, submitted*
- S. Chi*, H. Chi*, S. Chan, K. Ramani. Pose Relation Transformer Refine Occlusions for Human Pose Estimation. *IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA)*, 2023, Accepted
- [C2] H. Chi, M. H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Q. Huang, K. Ramani. InfoGCN: Representation Learning for Human Skeleton-based Action Recognition. IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2022
- [C1] M. H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Y. Cha, B. R. Moon. Evolution-based Meta Reinforcement Learning for Portfolio Optimization. In proceedings of the 23rd *The Genetic and Evolutionary Computation Conference (GECCO), 2021*

Research & Project

Skeleton-based action sequence generation with salient atomic actions

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ.

Dec. 2022 -

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

• Encode latent action trajectory with Neural ODE.

- · Extract the salient action frames of actions, and define atomic actions with the salient action frames.
- Apply diffusion model to generate continuous action sequences with atomic actions.

Weakly Supervised Action Segmentation for Video

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ.

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

- · Introduced a loss function for video segmentation combining Triplet loss and Temporal Cycle Consistency Loss
- Defined the Action Segmentation problem as a Neural Machine Translation problem
- · Visualized the attention matrices to interpret Machine's inference

Improving Multi-Joint dynamics with Contact(MuJoCo) by applying Hierarchical Reinforcement Learning

OptLab, Seoul National Univ.

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Sep. 2019 - Jul. 2020

July. 2020 - Sept. 2020

- · Proposed a hierarchical architecture to give the agent frequent reward signals by setting subgoals
- Designed and developed a hierarchical architecture of model and environment
- · Applied policy gradient with self-critical sequence training in optimization

Predicting stock price by applying Combinatorial Optimization

OptLab, Seoul National Univ.

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

- Analyzed data with the ANOVA(Analysis of variance) method and Regression method
- · Applied Genetic Algorithm, Evolutional Computation, and Fourier transformation to find better solutions
- Applied distributed computing to accelerate independent computation

Jan. 2019 - Jun. 2019

Accelerating computation of Machine Learning by using Field-Programmable Gate Array

ArchiLab, Seoul National Univ.

ArchiLab, Seoul National Univ.

Sep. 2018 - Dec. 2018

RESEARCH ASSISTANT Aug. 2018 - Jan. 2019

- · Applied methods of SIMD(Single Instruction Multiple Data) with the low-level language of Verilog
- Reduced data size with SVD(Singular Value Decomposition)
- Rearranged units to utilize parallel computation

Designing spatial-navigation on chrome-extension

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

- formulated malfunctioning cases and defined user-friendly environment
- Developed user-friendly navigation UI
- https://github.com/WICG/spatial-navigation

Skills

Research and Development Stacks

Major Languages Python, C/C++, java, Verilog Machine Learning PyTorch, TensorFlow **Computer Vision** OpenCV, OpenGL

Web Languages Nginx, HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS

Database MySQL, SQLite

Other Tools and Skills

Other Langauges Shell Scripts(bszh, zsh), Matlab, R **Operating Systems** macOS, Linux Debian/Ubuntu, Windows

Text Editors & IDE Vim, VSCode, Eclipse Software SolidWorks, Catia, AutoCAD

VCS Git

Working Experience

SK Hynix Icheon, S.Korea

Sep. 2017 - Dec. 2017 INTERN RESEARCHER

· Designed an exclusive chip for testing 3D NAND flash architecture and verified the reliabilty of existing architectures

• Developed a module for predicting locality of data and tested it with real data

Korean National Police Agency

Dokdo, S.Korea

DOKDO SECURITY POLICE Dec. 2013 - Sep. 2015

Defended the disputed territory as a squad leader

Teaching Experience

CS.4190.681A	Genetic Algorithm, 2019-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.4190.407	Algorithm, 2019-fall, 2020-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.M1522.407	Data Structure , 2019-spring, 2020-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.4190.308	Computer architecture, 2018-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.035.001	Digital Computer Concept and Practice , 2017-fall, 2018-fall	Teaching Assistant
PE.051.004	Volley ball, 2018-fall, 2019-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant

Honors & Awards

Competition of accelerating General-Purpose GPU sponsored by Intel

Manycore Programming Lab

1ST PLACE

Korea Ministry of Science and ICT

Mar. 2018 - Aug. 2021

The National Scholarship for Science and Engineering

FULL SCHOLARSHIP